<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Enchantment in the History of Capitalism</title>
    <link>https://askebos.github.io/econchants2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Enchantment in the History of Capitalism</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 08:21:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://askebos.github.io/econchants2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Enchantment in contemporary scholarship on economic life</title>
      <link>https://askebos.github.io/econchants2/events/roundtable-2022-05-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askebos.github.io/econchants2/events/roundtable-2022-05-05/</guid>
      <description>This event will be held on Zoom - please register on Eventbrite to attend
Speakers Professor Jean Comaroff, Harvard University
Professor Jens Beckert, Max Planck Institute
Professor Robert Kozinets, University of Southern California
Readings TBC</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enchantment in the history of science, literature, and art</title>
      <link>https://askebos.github.io/econchants2/events/roundtable-2022-03-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askebos.github.io/econchants2/events/roundtable-2022-03-25/</guid>
      <description>This event will be held on Zoom - please register on Eventbrite to attend
Speakers Professor David Morgan, Duke University
Professor Carrie Tirado Bramen, University at Buffalo
Readings   David Morgan, &amp;ldquo;Enchantment and Disenchantment&amp;rdquo; in Images at Work: The Material Culture of Enchantment (OUP, 2019).
  Christine Smallwood, &amp;ldquo;Astrology in the Age of Uncertainty&amp;rdquo; in The New Yorker, 28 October 2019.
  Nicholas Campion, &amp;ldquo;Introduction: Origins and Background&amp;rdquo; in A History of Western Astrology Volume II: The Medieval and Modern Worlds (Bloomsbury, 2009)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://askebos.github.io/econchants2/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 08:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askebos.github.io/econchants2/contact/</guid>
      <description>Join our mailing list here: ECONOMIC-ENCHANTMENTS@JISCMAIL.AC.UK
Do you have questions or suggestions? Get in touch with either Astrid (@askebos) or Anat (@anat_rosenberg; arosenberg [at] idc.ac.il).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://askebos.github.io/econchants2/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 08:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askebos.github.io/econchants2/people/</guid>
      <description>Network coordinators Anat Rosenberg is a senior lecturer at the Harry Radzyner Law School, Reichman University, Israel. Her work concerns the cultural legal history of capitalism, liberalism and consumption in Britain, and methodologies of law and the humanities. She is author of Liberalizing Contracts: Nineteenth Century Promises Through Literature, Law and History (2018), and The Rise of Mass Advertising: Law, Enchantment and the Cultural Boundaries of British Modernity (forthcoming).
Astrid Van den Bossche is Lecturer in Digital Marketing and Communications at the Department of Digital Humanities, King&amp;rsquo;s College London.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enchantment in theology and scholarship on magic</title>
      <link>https://askebos.github.io/econchants2/events/roundtable-2022-02-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askebos.github.io/econchants2/events/roundtable-2022-02-24/</guid>
      <description>Speakers Professor Owen Davies, University of Hertfordshire
Professor Jason Ānanda Josephson Storm, Williams College
Readings   Owen Davies, ‘Cunning-Folk in the Medical Market-Place during the Nineteenth Century’. Medical History 43, no. 1 (1999): 55–73.
  Owen Davies, &amp;ldquo;Chapter 7: Pulp magic&amp;rdquo; in Grimoires: A History of Magic Books (Oxford, 2009).
  Jason Ānanda Josephson Storm, “Max Weber and the Rationalization of Magic,” Yelle and Trein eds., in Narratives of Disenchantment and Secularization (Bloomsbury, 2020), pp.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
